A Guide to the Robert S. Bloxom Papers, 1978-2003
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Reports and Publications, 1981-2003., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 78-79)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government. "Improving Government Operations: Final Report on Efficiency, Regulatory Reform, and Privatization,." 1 January 1990. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. "2000 Annual Report on Status of Tributary Strategies, Chesapeake Bay Agreement, and Water Quality for Virginia's Chesapeake Bay and Tributaries," November 2000. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. "Eastern Shore Coastal Basins Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy," November 1999. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. " Initial James River Basin Tributary Nutrient and Sediment Reduction Strategy," 1 July 1998. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. "Rappahannock River and Northern Neck Coastal Basins Tributary Strategy Status Report," July 1998. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. "Tributary Strategy: Goals for Nutrient and Sediment Reduction in the James River," August 2000. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. "York River and Lower York Coastal Basins Draft Initial Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy," July 1998. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Secretary of Natural Resources. "York River and Lower York Coastal Basins Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy," February 2000. (Box 78)
  - "Fish Restoration and Passage on the James River." Virginia Wildlife Reprint, August 1992. (Box 78)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission. "Central and Regional Office Staffing in the Department of Corrections," 1984. (Box 78)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission. "Medicaid-Financed Long Term Care Services," 1993. (Box 78)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission. "Review of Elementary and Secondary School Funding," 20 November 2001. (Box 78)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission. "Review of State-Owned Real Property," 12 September 1994. (Box 78)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission. "Virginia's Progress Toward Chesapeake Bay Nutrient Reduction Goals," 9 December 1996. (Box 78)
  - Maryland. Governor's Commission on Growth in the Chesapeake Bay Region. "Technical Report, Working Papers, and Fiscal Studies (3 vols.)," January 1991. (Box 79)
  - Maryland Sea Grant College. "Dissolved Oxygen in the Chesapeake Bay: A Scientific Consensus.". (Box 79)
  - Massachusetts Department of Environmental Management. "Dealing with Change in the Connecticut River Valley: A Design Manual for Conservation and Development," December 1990. (Box 79)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration. "Aerospace Technology Enterprise: Annual Progress Report," 2002. (Box 79)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration. "Crafting Flight: Aircraft Pioneers and the Contributions of Men and Women of NASA Langley Research Center.". (Box 79)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration. "From Research to Relevance: Significant Achievements in Aeronautical Research at Langley Research Center (1917-2002).". (Box 79)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration. "Stakeholders Report: A Report to the American People," April 2003. (Box 79)
  - Price WaterhouseCoopers Endowment for the Business of Government Publications, 1999-2001 (Various Series). (Box 79)
  - Southeastern Virginia Planning District Commission. "Environmental Reviews," March 1990. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. "Chesapeake Basin Research Directory: Who's Who in Chesapeake Bay Research," March 1991. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. "Coastal Nonpoint Pollution Control Program: Program Development and Approval Guidance," January 1993. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. "Proceedings of the Delmarva Coastal Bays Conference III: Tri-State Approaches to Preserving Aquatic Resources," 12-13 November 1999. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. "Wetlands and 401 Certification: Opportunities and Guidelines for States and Eligible Indian Tribes," April 1989. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "Chesapeake Bay Communities: Making the Connection - A Catalog of Local Initiatives to Protect and Restore the Chesapeake Bay Watershed," April 1996. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "Chesapeake Bay Dissolved Oxygen Goal for Restoration of Living Resource Habitats," December 1992. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "Cost of Providing Government Services to Alternative Residential Patterns," May 1993. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "Perspectives on Chesapeake Bay: Market-based Strategies for Chesapeake Bay Policy and Management," May 1996. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "Recent Wetland Status and Trends in the Chesapeake Watershed (1982 to 1989): Technical Report," May 1994. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "The State of the Chesapeake Bay: A Report to the Citizens of the Bay Region." July 2002. (Box 79)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency. Chesapeake Bay Program. "Submerged Aquatic Vegetation Policy for the Chesapeake Bay and Tidal Tributaries," July 1989. (Box 79)
  - United States Government Printing Office. "The Clean Water Act as Amended by the Water Quality Act of 1987.". (Box 79)
  - University of Virginia. Institute of Government. "Judicial Review of Local Land Use Decisions in Virginia," 1981. (Box 79)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. College of Architecture and Urban Studies. "Case Studies of Local Water Resources Management in Virginia," March 1991. (Box 79)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. College of Architecture and Urban Studies. "Multijurisdictional Approaches to Managing Water Resources: Options for Virginia Localities," March 1991. (Box 79)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. Virginia Water Resources Research Center. "Threats to Virginia's Groundwater," 1989. (Box 79)
  - "Virginia Wildlife," February 1995. (Box 79)